我要迟到了
I'm late.
这显示板坏了
This board is broken.
这显示板怎么坏了
The arrivals board is not working.
有人看到从危地马拉来的航班吗
Uh, did anybody meet the flight from Guatemala?
危地马拉航空公司 几号登机口
Aviateca Airlines? What gate?
我来晚了
I'm late.
打扰下
Excuse me, uh...
航班显示板出现了点故障
you have a computer glitch at the arrivals board.
你好
Hello?
先生 打扰一下
Sir, excuse me, yoo-hoo.
很好
Great.
哟 你好呀
Yeah. Hi.
从危地马拉来的航班
The flight from Guatemala.
告诉我你事先说过"打扰一下"
Tell me you tried "Excuse me" First.
亲爱的 我当然说过了
Sweetie! Yes, I did!
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
你累不累啊
Oh! Are you exhausted?
危地马拉是不是很糟
Was Guatemala awful?
是不是非常落后
Was it horribly backward?
但我还没落后到要秀胸部获取信息
And yet, I was never reduced to flashing my boobs for information.
为了啥好玩的原因秀的吗
Flash them for any fun reasons?
我一直在乱葬岗里埋头苦干
I was literally neck deep in a mass grave.
一点也不浪漫
Not romantic.
一头跳进一堆死尸中
Diving head first in a pit of cadavers
是搞不定你一团糟的分手的
is no way to handle a messy break-up.
Angela 我和Pete从没一团糟过
Angela, nothing Pete and I ever did was messy.
那你当时就做错了
Then you were not doing the right thing.
先生 你跟着我们干嘛
Sir, why are you following us?
遇袭啊 救命啊 快来人啊
Attack! Security! Hello!
这机场谁管的啊
Who runs this airport?
狠狠教训他
Kick his ass.
- 退后  - 是他攻击我的
- Step back now!  - He attacked me.
我是国土安全部的
I'm Homeland Security!
这是个小误会
Oh... little misunderstanding here.
你们可以把枪收起来了
You can put away your guns.
什么时候你们都归她管了
What, is she in charge now?
什么时候放下武器 我说了算
No, I'll tell you when you can lower your weapons.
把包交出来
Hand over the bag.
就为了这个
Is that what this is about?
我是Dr. Temperance Brennan
I am Dr. Temperance Brennan.
我待在危地马拉两个月
I've been in Guatemala for two months,
鉴别种族大屠杀遇难者的身份 也包括他
identifying victims of genocide, including him.
这种情况下大多数人
Most people in this situation,
都会出一身冷汗
what they do is they sweat it.
危地马拉种族大屠杀
Guatemala? Genocide?
经过那些你还会害怕吗
How are you scary after that?
- 你知道谁会不冒冷汗吗  - 反社会人士
- You know who doesn't sweat it? - Sociopaths.
我不是反社会人士
I'm not a sociopath.
我是Jeffersonian的人类学家
I'm an anthropologist at the Jeffersonian.
还为FBI工作
Who works for the FBI.
或许我会相信这些
Which I'd maybe believe you
前提是你说的身份能让你进餐厅以外的地方
if you had ID that did more than allowed you access to the cafeteria.
女士 你这是非法运输人类遗体
You are illegally transporting human remains, ma'am.
你还袭击了一名国土安全部探员
And you assaulted a Homeland Security agent.
抱歉让你在朋友面前丢人了
Look, I'm sorry if I embarrassed you in front of your friends,
但下次攻击我之前 你该先表明身份
but next time, you should identify yourself before attacking me.
你来这干嘛
What are you doing here?
FBI特别探员Seeley Booth
FBI. Special Agent Seeley Booth,
华盛顿重案组
Major Crime Investigation, DC.
Bones为我们鉴定尸体身份
Bones identifies bodies for us.
别叫我Bones
Don't call me Bones.
我不单单鉴定的
And I do more than identify.
她还写书
She also writes books.
好吧 她归你了
Fine. She's all yours.
很好 带上你的头骨 我们闪人
Great. Let's grab your skull, and let's vamoose.
就这样 她归你了
What, that's it? "She's all yours"?
那你为什么拦下我
Why did you stop me?
有关系吗 你可以离开了
What does it matter? You're free to go.
只要带上你的包
Just grab your bags.
- 快点 快点  - 你故意设计我
- Click, click, kling, kling. - You set me up.
FBI让你审问我的 是不
You got a hold-for-questioning request from the FBI, didn't you?
我喜欢这书
I love this book.
走吧
Come on.
你就这点本事
That's the best you can do?
什么
What?
让国土安全部的人抓我
Getting Homeland Security to snatch me
你好来个英雄救美的戏码
so you can stage a fake rescue?
怎么说我也来机场接你了 对吧
Well, at least I picked you up at the airport, huh?
行了 我用过正当渠道找你
Come on, I mean, I went through the appropriate channels,
但是你的助手百般阻挠
but your assistant there, he stone-walled me.
没错 经过上次的案子
Yeah, well, after the last case,
我告诉Zack要对你守口如瓶
I told Zack never ever to put you through.
他是个很好的助手
He's a good assistant.
你在这随便找个地方让我下车
You can let me out anywhere along here.
今早在阿灵顿国家公墓
Listen, a decomposed corpse was found
发现了一具腐烂的尸体
this morning at Arlington National Cemetery.
阿灵顿国家公墓本来就都是腐烂的尸体
Arlington National Cemetery is full of decomposed corpses.
那是个墓地
It's a cemetery.
没错 但这个是你的那一型
Yeah, but this one is your type of corpse,
不是棺材里的那种
it wasn't in a casket.
你再开一个街区
If you drive one more block
我就朝窗外喊"绑架"
I'm screaming "Kidnap" Out the window.
- 我在试着沟通  - 靠边停车
- You know what, I'm trying to mend bridges here. - Pull over.
- 我要回家了  - 很好
- I'm going home. - Great.
我们能不能...能不能直接跳过这部分
Could we... Look, could we just skip this part?
我发现你这人有一种优越感
I find you very condescending.
我? 有优越感吗
Me? I'm condescending?
我可不像某人
I'm not the one who's got to mention
每五分钟就要说到她有个博士学位
that she's got a doctorate every five minutes.
我确实是有博士学位
I am the one with a doctorate.
没错 但是我也有警徽和枪
Yeah, but I'm the one with the badge and the gun.
你又不是城里唯一的法医人类学家
You're not the only forensic anthropologist in town.
我还真是的 最近的那个在蒙特利尔(加拿大魁北克省)
Yes, I am. The next nearest is in Montreal.
你会说法语吗
Parlez-vous Francais?
到底要怎样啊你
What's it going to take, huh?
- 全程参与案子  - 行
- Full participation in the case. - Fine.
不只是实验室工作 每一项都要参与
Not just lab work, everything.
要在我手上吐口水吗 那样我们就成Scully和Mulder了
Well you want me to spit in my hand? We're Scully and Mulder.
我不明白这是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
意思就是 咱讲和吧
It's an olive branch.
回车上去吧
Just get back in the car.
怎么发现尸体的
What's the context of the find?
例行环境绿化
Routine landscaping
他们在降低池塘的水位
they drop the level of the pond,
一个工人觉得他看到什么东西
one of the workmen thought he saw something.
Scully和Mulder:《X档案》男女主角
嗨 Zack
Hi, Zack.
- 这身生态卫士装很适合你  - 谢谢
- This eco-warrior look works for you. - Thanks.
很运动型
Very action-oriented.
Booth探员 还记得我助手Zack Addy吗
Agent Booth, you remember my assistant, Zack Addy?
必须记得
Oh, yeah.
在危地马拉怎么样
How was Guatemala?
你挖出许多大屠杀遇难者遗体了
You dig up lots of massacred victims?
学到点弯刀小知识了没
Learn a thing or two about machete strikes?
Zack 我需要一些池塘水样
Zack, I need water samples
还有水温数据
and temperature readings from the pond.
马上去 Dr. Brennan
Right away, Dr. Brennan.
那孩子没啥眼力
He's got no sense of discretion, that kid.
典型的眯眯眼
Typical squint.
我不懂你的意思
I don't know what that means.
警察束手无策时 我们就会找你这类人
Well, cops get stuck, we bring in people like you.
我们称之 眯眯眼
You know-- squints...
眯着眼睛看东西
you know, who squint at things.
你的意思是高智商
Oh, you mean people with very high IQs
有基本推理能力的人
and basic reasoning skills.
没错
Yeah.
我现在该眯眼看啥
What, exactly, am I supposed to be squinting at?
就像看爱情动作片
It's like pornography.
你看到的时候你就知道了
You'll know it when you see it.
好了 没错
Yeah, Ok...
这是犯罪现场
This is a crime scene.
尸体被0.1毫米厚的
The remains are wrapped in four-mil flat
聚酯纤维建筑薄膜包裹着
poly construction sheeting.
聚氯乙烯包住的铁丝网
PVC-coated chicken wire.
增加了质量
Weighted.
因此尸体腐烂过程中没有浮上来
That's why the body didn't surface during decomposition.
骨架是完整的 但头骨碎了
The skeleton is complete, but the skull is in fragments.
- 得出啥结论了  - 不多
- What can you tell me? - Not much.
年轻女性
She's a young woman,
大概18到22岁
probably between 18 and 22,
一米六左右
approximately five foot three,
人种不详 长得还不错
race unknown, delicate features.
就这些
That's all?
还是网球运动员
Tennis player.
你怎么知道她是个漂亮的网球运动员
How do you get a pretty tennis player out of that yuck?
从骺融合判断年龄
Epiphysis fusion gives age.
从骨盆形状能判断性别
Pelvic bone shape gives sex.
肩部有滑囊炎
Bursitis in the shoulder.
而且这么年轻 肯定是运动型损伤
Somebody this young, it must be an athletic injury.
死亡时间呢
When did she die?
- 嗯... - 嗯是什么意思
- Eh... - "Eh"?! What does that even mean?
这要等我们虫子粘土男查看后才知道
Means wait until our bug and slime guy takes a look.
无衣物
No clothing.
在我们这行来看
You know, in my line of work,
没衣服通常意味着性犯罪
no clothes usually means a sex crime.
在我们这行来看
In my line of work,
也意味着受害者喜欢穿天然纤维衣服
it can also mean the victim favored natural fibers.
比如你的外套 会比你的骨头经久数十年
Your suit, for example, will outlast your bones by decades.
收集淤泥 搜索范围半径3米深度10厘米
Collect silt, three meters radius to a depth of ten centimeters.
你们FBI法医组可以带走塑料布和铁丝网
Your FBI forensics team can take the plastic and the chicken wire,
剩下部分我们带走
we'll take the rest.
Dr. Goodman 我希望你别把我丢给FBI
Dr. Goodman, I wish you wouldn't just give me to the FBI.
作为联邦资助的机构
As a federally funded institution,
Jeffersonian必须抓住一切机会
the Jeffersonian must seize every opportunity
向国会朋友们证明我们的价值
to prove our worth to our friends in Congress,
所以我把你借出去是合适的
which means I loan you out as I see fit,
尤其是对联邦机构来说
especially to federal agencies.
"借出去"是指财产 Dr. Goodman
"Loan out" Implies property, Dr. Goodman.
FBI是不会尊重财产的
The FBI will never respect mere property.
Dr. Brennan 我没有把你看作财产
I do not view you as property, Dr. Brennan.
你是Jeffersonian最有价值的资产之一
You are one of the Jeffersonian's most valuable assets.
从定义上看 资产就是财产
An asset is, by definition, property.
Mr. Addy 我们的规矩是什么
What's the rule, Mr. Addy?
你只跟博士讲话
You only converse with PhDs.
你知道我俩博士都快读完了
You realize I'm halfway through two doctorates?
俩一半等于一个 所以从数学上说...
Two halves make a whole, so mathematically speaking...
Mr. Addy 去把骨头擦干净
Go polish a bone, Mr. Addy.
Dr. Goodman
Dr. Goodman,
如果你把科学家当临时工派给他们
FBI agents will never respect any of us
FBI的人永远都不会尊重我们的
as long as you simply dole out scientists like office temps.
Dr. Brennan
Dr. Brennan,
你在耍我吗
are you playing me?
你知道我不擅长那个
You know I'm no good at that.
以前是这样
Mmm. Thus far.
但是你的学习能力让人不安啊
But you have a disturbingly steep learning curve.
池塘是温的 充满微生物
The pond is not only warm and teeming with microbes,
这点加速了分解
which accelerated decomposition,
而且池塘里的青鱼和锦鲤 把尸体当点心
but it houses black carp and koi, which fed on the body.
作为这间屋里唯一的正常人
Can I, as the only normal person in this room,
我能说一句"真恶心"吗
say, "Ew"?
我发现三个时期的石蛾和摇蚊幼虫
I got three larval stages of Tricoptera, Chironimidae...
说重点
As we cut to the chase...
尸体在池塘里泡了一年多
The body was in the pond one winter and two summers.
从去年春天开始的
Spring before last?
你真的认为我精力旺盛吗
Do you really think I'm lusty?
他指在书里
The book.
绝对不是 你不在我书里面
No, no, no, you're not in the book.
他当然在 我们都在书里
Sure he is, we all are.
才没有 你们全都不在书里
No, none of you are in the book.
那些是虚构的角色
Those are fictitious characters based on...
淤泥里还找到一些小的骨头碎片
I found some small bone fragments in the silt.
现在我们从书里出来 回到现实
We're out of the book now. We're back in real life.
我猜是林蛙
I'd guess Rana temporaria.
青蛙骨头
Frog bones?
还有一些小金环 像从一条链上掉下的
Also, some tiny gold links, as from a fine chain.
澄清一下
Point of clarification--
我不是处男
I'm not a virgin.
早就不是了
Nowhere near, in fact.
Booth才是你刻画最完美的人物
Who you captured perfectly is Booth.
穿着传统刻板
Buttoned down, but...
内心放浪闷骚
buckets of sexual confidence which...
看的我都想要拍一下他屁股
oh, I, for one, would love to tap.
在泡水人面前讨论拍屁股不好吧
It's not right to discuss tapping asses in front of the soaker.
我无法在书和现实之间跳来跳去
I can't bounce back and forth between my book and real life.
既然我们现实中有案子 那就先别提书
Since we're stuck with real life, let's just forget the book.
我还没分析受害人手里的是什么
I haven't analyzed whatever it was the victim was holding in her hand,
但是看起来像是纤维素
but it looks like cellulose.
纸么
Paper?
可能吧
Hmm. Possibly.
我发现有极小的沙砾嵌在头骨碎片里
I found microscopic grit embedded in the skull fragments.
你也去鉴定一下
I need you to identify those, too.
把剩下的组织去掉
Remove the remaining tissue,
我来处理头骨碎片
I'll debride the skull fragments myself,
重组好后 Angela就能做面部重建了
reassemble it so Angela can put a face on our victim.
太好了 我更喜欢对着全息图
Good. I prefer holographs.
它们不臭
They don't stink.
Zack
Zack...
我不喜欢那些对遗体的措辞
I don't like those terms for human remains--
"泡水人" "脆皮人"
"Soaker," "Crispy critter..."
我知道了 Dr. Brennan
I know, Dr. Brennan.
这么说你让一个眯眯眼
So, you guaranteed a squint
参与谋杀案调查了
a field role in an active murder investigation?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
- 就是写这本书的人  - 没错
- The one that wrote the book? - Yes, sir.
我记得你说过她不再和你搭档了吧
Thought you said she wouldn't work with you anymore.
我们合作的上个案子中
The last case we worked,
她提供了对凶器和凶手的描述
she provided a description of the murder weapon and the murderer,
但我当时不太信她
but I didn't give her much credence.
为什么不
Why not?
因为她只看了尸检报告的X光图
Because she did it by looking at the victim's autopsy X rays.
要是这样 我也不会信她
Well, I wouldn't give it much credence, either.
但结果证明她都对了
Turns out she was right on both.
再加上这次 池塘里的受害人
Plus, the pond victim--
Brennan给出了年龄 性别 和喜爱的运动
Brennan gives me the victim's age, sex and favorite sport.
- 是什么  - 网球
- Which is?  - Tennis.
-她挺不错哦  - 不 她太棒了
- She's good. - No, she's amazing.
唯一能让她重新帮我的方法
Only way I can get her back on my side
只有带她去出外勤
is to bring her out in the field...
我愿意这么做
I'm willing.
没问题 她由你负责
Fine. She's on you.
带个眯眯眼出外勤 你得负全责
Take a squint out in the field, she's your responsibility.
遵命
Yes, sir.
Peter
Peter?
我回来的第一天 你就来取电视机
It's not rational for you to choose the first day I'm back
这一点都不理智
to reclaim your television.
你走了以后 我想了很多分手的原因
While you were away, I thought a lot about why we broke up.
我们整天吵架 相看两相厌了呗
We fought all the time and don't like each other anymore.
我们吵架是因为你感情上冷淡
We fought because you were emotionally distant and cold.
但嘿咻方面 我想你会同意
But sexually speaking, I think you'll agree...
你不是来拿电视的 你是掐好时间来嘿咻的
You didn't come for your TV. You timed this for a booty call.
好了 你该走了
Okay, you're leaving.
你的亲密障碍可能是因为你很小就成了孤儿
Your intimacy issues are probably due to being orphaned so young.
我恨心理学 你个饥渴男
I hate psychology, and you're just horny.
Brennan 你真的想要孤独余生吗
Brennan, do you really want to spend the rest of your life alone?
我不知道我的余生是怎样
I don't know about the rest of my life,
但我特么确定我现在想一个人待着
but I sure as hell wish I was alone right now.
那这样 我们一起分担电视的钱
So, what? We split the cost of the TV?
不送
Good-bye.
干嘛
What?
Angela 这真有趣
This is interesting, Angela.
早上好
Good morning.
Booth知道这玩意怎么工作吗
Does Booth know how this works?
我设计的这个电脑程序
This computer program, which I designed--
正在申请专利
patent pending--
它接受一整组的数字输入
accepts a full array of digital input,
对其进行处理
processes it and then projects it
然后输出三维全息图像
as a three-dimensional holographic image.
- 明白  - 你明白了
- Okay.  - You get that?
当然 申请专利那部分
Yeah, the patent pending part.
Brennan重组了头骨然后标记了组织
Brennan reassembled the skull and applied tissue markers.
头骨损坏的很严重 但是种族特征
Her skull was badly damaged, but racial indicators--
即颧骨尺寸 鼻弓 枕骨尺寸
cheekbone dimensions, nasal arch, occipital measurements--
表明是非洲裔美国人
suggest African-American.
接下来
And...
这就是受害人
we have our victim.
我不得不承认 这太酷了
I have to admit, that's pretty cool.
Ange 重来一次 换成白人数值
Ange, rerun the program substituting Caucasian values.
你们不觉得她眼熟吗
Does she look familiar to anyone?
不觉得
No.
折中一下 试试混血
Split the difference. Mixed race.
Lenny Kravitz那种还是Vanessa Williams那种
Lenny Kravitz or Vanessa Williams?
Lenny Kravitz: 90年代美国摇滚男歌手
Vanessa Williams: 首位有非裔血统的美国小姐
我不知道你是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
Angela 减少颧骨到下巴的组织深度
Angela, reduce tissue depth over the cheekbones to the jawline.
有人认出她是谁了吗
Does anyone recognize her?
- 我没有  - 等一下
- Not me.  - Wait.
是我想的那个人吗
Is that who I think it is?
那个和议员有一腿的女孩
The girl who had the affair with the Senator?
她叫Cleo Louise Eller
Her name's Cleo Louise Eller...
Ted和Sharon Eller的独生女
only daughter to Ted and Sharon Eller.
最后一次出现是2003年4月6日晚上9点左右
Last seen approximately 9:00 p.M., April 6 2003,
从K街的Cardio Deluxe Jam离开
leaving the Cardio Deluxe Jam on K Street.
她甚至没回到车里
She didn't even make it to her car.
记忆力真好
Pretty good memory.
我的工作是找到她
Yeah, well, it's my job to find her.
这样的话 恭喜你成功了
In that case, congratulations on your success.
这绝对不是我希望的结局
This isn't exactly the way I wanted it to end.
Cleo Eller可不是一般的失踪女孩
Cleo Eller is not just some missing girl.
是的 她是参议院的实习生
Yeah, she's a senate intern
还和Allan Bethlehem议员睡过
who was boinking Senator Allan Bethlehem.
对她的失踪调查中
I was secondary in the investigation
我是个副手
into the disappearance of that girl,
我们无法确认这点
and we couldn't confirm that.
不知道她长相前 你怎么认出她的
How did you recognize her before she even had her own face?
我看得出她特征的基础构架
I recognized the underlying architecture of her features,
剩下的对我只是装饰而已
the rest is just window dressing.
我不是专家 但他不应该更高兴点吗
I'm not an expert, but shouldn't he be happier?
不 相信我 我很高兴
Oh, no, believe me, I'm happy.
我看你是挺高兴的
You seem happy to me.
这件事给我保密
I need this kept quiet.
看 掩饰真相
Ah, cover-up.
妄想阴谋论
Paranoid conspiracy theory.
Monica Lewinsky: 克林顿性丑闻的女主角
克格勃: 苏联情报机构
那我觉得Monica Lewinsky
Is it paranoia that Monica Lewinsky
是克格勃培训的性爱间谍也算妄想吗
was a KGB-trained sex-agent mole?
如果我能让一切运转正常(按序排列鸭子) 或许能当案子的负责人
if I line all my ducks up in a row, I can maybe head it up.
我不懂你在说什么 但我可以做只鸭子
I don't know what that means, but I think I can be a duck.
你可不是什么鸭子 好吧
You're not a duck. Okay?
这次我们得按规矩来
On this one, we stick to the book.
警察出外勤 眯眯眼做实验
Cops on the streets, squints in the lab.
那样的话 Jeffersonian就发篇新闻稿
In that case, the Jeffersonian will be issuing a press release
公开池塘里女孩的身份了
identifying the girl in the pond.
你那么干的话 我就是只废鸭了
You do that, I'm a dead duck.
你想干什么
What are you trying to do?
勒索你
Blackmail you.
勒索一位联邦探员?
Blackmail a federal agent?
就是
Yes.
我不喜欢这个
I don't like it.
我知道你不喜欢
I'm fairly certain you're not supposed to.
好吧 算你一个
Fine, you're in.
你确定那是Cleo Eller吗
You're certain it's Cleo Eller?
情况完全吻合 年龄 种族 身高
The profile's dead on : age, race, height.
还有 时间也对的上
Plus, the timeline fits.
Cleo Eller大学时候确实打网球
I mean, Cleo Eller did play tennis in college.
跟我说说那个参议员
Talk to me about the Senator.
死者Cleo Eller曾为议员Bethlehem工作
Cleo Eller, the victim, worked for Senator Bethlehem.
有消息传他们有性关系
It was reported that they were involved sexually.
我们无法确认这点
We couldn't confirm that.
Bethlehem很卑鄙 人人都知道
Well, Bethlehem's a hound. Everybody knows that.
Cleo的男友 Ken Thompson
Ken Thompson, Cleo's boyfriend.
Thompson现在还是Bethlehem的助理
Thompson's still Bethlehem's aide.
Thompson负责Bethlehem的日程
Thompson keeps Bethlehem's calendar.
议员有外遇的话
No way the Senator has an affair
Thompson不可能不知道的
that Thompson doesn't know about.
没有性关系 就没动机
No sexual relationship, no motive.
那个疯子呢
What about the nut case?
Oliver Laurier
Oliver Laurier.
这案子里你觉得他怎么样
Do you like him for this?
他是个跟踪狂
He's a stalker.
你第一步打算做什么
What's your first move?
我想告知Eller夫妇 他们女儿找到了
I'd like to inform the Ellers that we found their daughter.
这事还是保密比较好
It's better to keep this quiet.
已经过了有两年了吧
It's been, what, two years?
再过几天也不要紧吧
What's another few days?
恕我直言 我和这家人挺熟的
All due respect, sir, I've come to know the family pretty well,
特别是少校
especially the Major,
两年未果实在是太久了
and two years is a hell of a long time in limbo.
今天下午以前我会得出死因细节
I'll have details of cause of death by this afternoon.
我们就从那开始着手
That's where we'll get started.
好吧
All right.
Hodgins鉴定出
Hodgins identified the particulates
嵌在Cleo Eller头骨里的微粒是轧钢
embedded in Cleo Eller's skull as rolled steel--
很大可能来自一柄大锤
most likely from a sledge-type hammer.
另外 微粒还有水泥和硅藻土
Also, there's cement and diatomaceous earth.
- 那是啥 - 看起来就像这个
- What's that? - Looks like that.
由史前海洋生物组成
It's made up of prehistoric sea creatures.
常被用作杀虫剂 过滤剂
It's used as an insecticide, filtering agent,
清洁磨料 陶器材料什么的
cleaning abrasive, ceramics.
很常见
It's very common.
常不常见 硅藻土都是条线索
Diatomaceous earth common or not, it's a clue.
你确定是我们Cleo吗
You're positive it's our Cleo?
我们找到22个对比匹配点
We established 22 matching points of comparison...
是的   我们确定
Yes... We're certain.
是他干的吗
Did he do it?
那个参议员
The Senator?
两个军人之间的实话实说
One military man to another?
Eller少校 我们不能以任何方式谈论调查
Major Eller, we can't discuss the investigation in any way.
那至少告诉我们 她走得痛苦吗
Can you at least tell us if our daughter suffered?
从她头骨的状况判断
Given the state of her skull...
Cleo走得不痛苦
Cleo never saw it coming.
谢谢你
Thank you.
Mrs. Eller 能否告知 Cleo脖子上戴的什么
Mrs. Eller, could you tell us what Cleo wore around her neck?
她爸爸的青铜星章
Her father's Bronze Star.
Ted在第一次海湾战争赢得的
Ted won it in the first Gulf War,
他把这个给她希望她好运
and he gave it to her for luck.
他们应该知道真相
Those people deserve the truth.
他们女儿被杀
Their daughter was murdered.
他们应得的是善意的谎言
They deserve the kindness of a lie.
最后总还有调查报告
There will be an inquest report.
他们不会看的 因为他们不会想看
Which they won't read because they don't want to.
特别是最后那段日子
Especially because toward the end,
Cleo和她父母连话都不说了
Cleo and her parents weren't even speaking.
他们跟你说的吗
They told you that?
从活生生的人身上获取信息
Getting information out of live people is
和从一堆骨头上取得信息差别可大了
a lot different than getting information out of a pile of bones.
你得先提供点自己的什么情况
You have to offer up something of yourself first.
你在军队里到底是做什么的
What exactly did you do in the military?
看吧 看你刚才干嘛了 Bones
See? See what you did right there, Bones?
你问了个私人问题
You asked a personal question
却没有交换你的个人情况
without offering anything personal in return.
既然我不是骨架
And since I'm not a skeleton,
那么你什么都得不到 对不起咯
you get zilch. Sorry.
这里有些刺痕
There are stab marks here.
指骨末端还有奇怪痕迹
And odd markings on the distal phalanges.
我从未见过的
Nothing I've seen before.
简单来说  焦虑 抑郁 还想吐
In a nutshell? Anxious, depressed and nauseous.
- 请天病假吧  - 不是我 是Cleo Eller
- Take a sick day. - Not me. Cleo Eller.
虫壳化验显示她正服用氯羟安定
Beatle casings show she was on Lorazepam,
利眠宁 盐酸敏克静
Chlordiazepoxide and Meclizine Hydrochloride.
恶心反胃
Nausea...
让我看看那些碎骨
Show me those bone fragments.
这些不是青蛙骨头
These aren't frog bones.
Cleo Eller怀孕了
Cleo Eller was pregnant.
- 胎儿的遗骸吗  - 锤骨 砧骨 镫骨
- Fetal remains? - Malleus, incus, stapes.
这些是胎儿的耳骨
These are fetal ear bones.
- 这女孩怀孕了  - 刚怀不久
- The girl was pregnant. - Not very far along.
要我做DNA检测吗
You want me to try and get a DNA reading,
看能不能确认胎儿父亲
see if we can prove paternity?
你可以试试 希望有足够的样本做基因试验
You can try. Let's hope there's enough genetic material to test.
这议员很狡猾嘛
This Senator, oh, he is smart.
他把一个实习生肚子搞大了
He gets an intern pregnant,
然后这事威胁到他事业了 就杀掉她
then murders her when it threatens his career.
他还有关系可以逃脱处罚
And he has the connections to get away with it.
我讨厌你把猜想说的跟真的一样
I hate it when you make paranoia plausible.
停都停不住
It's like sliding off a cliff.
特别调查组 你那个FBI伙伴别想当带头人了
This special unit, no way your FBI pal heads it up,
除非掌权的恶势力确信
unless the dark powers in charge are convinced
他知道他的政治前途在哪里
he knows where his political bread is buttered.
不管怎样 这个调查是到头了
Either way, that's where this investigation ends.
想去喝点什么不
Want to get a drink?
不谈案子
Non-topical application?
哼哼 哈嘿
Glug-glug, whoo-hoo!
好了 亲爱的
Come on, sweetie.
要是Booth是对的怎么办
What if Booth's right?
要是我只对骨头在行 不会与人交往
What if I'm only good with bones and lousy with people?
人们都喜欢你
People like you.
我才不管男人喜不喜欢我
I don't care if men like me.
从人们变成男人 有趣的跳转
Okay, interesting leap from "People" To "Men,"
但我确定那没啥深意
but I'm sure it means nothing.
我讨厌心理学
I hate psychology.
我最有意义的联系都是和死人建立的
My most meaningful relationships are with dead people.
- 谁说的  - 可这是真的
- Who said that? - It's true.
我只见到Cleo的骨头 我就了解她了
I understand Cleo, and her bones are all I've ever seen.
7岁的时候 她摔断了手腕
When she was seven, she broke her wrist,
可能是因为从单车上摔下来吧
probably falling off a bike,
两星期后 石膏都还没拆下来
and two weeks later, before the cast was even removed,
她又去骑单车 然后手腕再次骨折
she got right back on that bike and broke it all over again.
还有她被害的时候
And when she was being murdered,
她拼命地反抗 尽管...
she fought back hard even though...
她很绝望 她可能活不到明天
...she was so depressed she could hardly get up in the morning.
她并不想死
She didn't welcome death.
Cleo想活下去
Cleo wanted to live.
亲爱的
Honey...
你有没有想过别那么纠结
you ever think that maybe you come off a little distant
因为你实在太过投入了
because you connect too much?
我讨厌心理学 那都是软科学
I hate psychology. It's a soft science.
我懂的 但是
I know, but...
人大都是软的
people are mostly soft.
除了他们的骨头
Except for their bones.
是啊
Yeah.
想要点建议吗
You want some advice?
哼哼 哈嘿?
Glug-glug, whoo-hoo?
偶尔倾诉一下自己的一些事
Offer up a little bit of yourself every once in a while.
就是
Just...
跟别人说点什么
tell somebody something
即使你不知道自己想不想让人了解
you're not completely certain you want them to know.
这是我第二次听见这个建议了
That's the second time I've received that advice.
你知道我的建议都很棒的
Well, you know I give great advice.
看来我得加把油试试了
I'm going to have to push this to the next level.
我很奇怪
I'm a little confused as to
为什么FBI的头头会派你来
why the Director of the FBI would send you
跟议员谈话 而不是他自己来
to speak to the Senator instead of coming himself.
可能是因为我是
Probably because I'm the one
发现Cleo Eller怀孕了的人
that found that Cleo Eller was pregnant.
你能从骸骨里得知那女孩怀孕了
You could tell the girl was pregnant from her skeleton?
我们找到了胎儿的骨头
We found fetal bones.
议员 唯一的问题是你们谁是父亲
The only question, Senator, is which one of you is the father.
你们愿意做个DNA检测吗
Are you willing to submit to a DNA test?
从敏感性上考虑
You know what? Given the sensitivity,
律师不在场的话 什么都别说
don't say anything on the subject without your attorney present,
这是我的建议
that's my advice.
也是我想采纳的建议
Advice I intend to take.
Ken 我们还有个表决要去呢
Ken, we have a vote to get to.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
口香糖上的唾液 可是不错的DNA来源
Saliva, say from chewing gum, is an excellent source of DNA.
正好拿来和胎儿骨头的DNA做对比
I intend to compare it to the DNA in the fetal bones.
你要有搜查令才行
You need a warrant for that.
Ken 她必须要有搜查令
Ken. She needs a warrant.
需要进一步问话时 我们会联系你的
We have any further questions, we'll be in touch.
Ken
Ken.
现在我就能将你逮捕归案
I could place you under arrest on a federal charge right now
罪名就是恐吓美国议员
for uttering threats against a United States senator.
- 什么  - Bones
- What? - Bones.
- 她归我管 但你对她负责 - 是 长官
- I own her, but she was your responsibility. - Yes, sir.
让特别探员Furst进来
Send in Special Agent Furst.
我早就警告你别带眯眯眼出外勤
I warned you about taking squints out to the field,
但你打了包票 说她不会搞砸的
but you vouched for her, said she wouldn't screw up.
- 是的长官  - 不是这样的
- Yes, sir. - No, no.
Booth并不知道我要去见议员
Booth didn't know that I was going to see the Senator.
我想要份他的DNA样本
I wanted to get a sample of his DNA.
- 是啊  - 帮倒忙呢
- Exactly.  - Not helping.
明早我会宣布成立一个特别小组
Tomorrow morning I'm announcing the formation of a special unit
来跟进Cleo Eller的案子
to investigate the murder of Cleo Eller,
届时你的调查将正式终止
at which time your investigation will be officially terminated.
你也不会领导新的小组
You will not head the new unit.
祝贺你 Patrick
Congratulations, Patrick.
- 别生我气啊  - 不会
- No hard feelings.  - Right.
明早我需要全部的卷宗
I need the complete case files in the morning.
当然 会准备好
Of course. They'll be ready.
谢了 Furst探员
Thank you, Agent Furst.
至少Dr. Brennan知道了
Well, at least Dr. Brennan found out
Bethlehem议员和Cleo有染
that Senator Bethlehem was having sex with Cleo.
我有吗
I did?
报告显示胎儿的遗骨
The report said there wasn't enough DNA
没有足够的DNA确定亲子关系
in the fetal bones to determine paternity.
可议员并不想Dr. Brennan拿到口香糖
Senator Bethlehem didn't want Dr. Brennan to take that gum.
他在隐藏什么
He's hiding something.
他不知道DNA不足
He didn't know there wasn't enough DNA.
Dr. Brennan 我觉着你还是
I suggest that you, uh, go back to your lab,
回你的实验室 做好本职吧
Dr. Brennan, and get used to being there.
走吧 Bones
Come on, Bones.
你还好吧
You OK?
别这么客气 我给你惹了麻烦
Don't be nice to me after I got you in trouble.
你也是出于好心
Your heart was in the right place.
我不是感性之人 你才是
I'm not a heart person. You're a heart person.
我可是理性至上的
I'm a brain person.
- 你为我担保了  - 算了吧
- You vouched for me. - Forget it.
不行
No, I won't.
你认为是议员干的吗
You think it was the Senator?
议员跟一票实习生都胡搞
The Senator's had sex with a dozen of these interns
也没见他杀了谁
and he hasn't killed any of them.
我觉得跟踪狂嫌疑最大
My best bet is still the stalker.
你想查查他吗
You want to check him out?
我们能...你咋说的来着 收擦他
We can, um, what do you call it, roost him?
- 搜查... - 搜查
- Roust... - Roust.
凶手抢走了Cleo的青铜星章 所以...
The murderer snatched the Bronze Star from Cleo's neck, so...
我还剩12个小时移交这案子
I got 12 hours before this case is over and I'm off it,
所以 咱去会会他 走
so let's go roust him. Come on.
Mr. Laurier 我们授权搜查你的住...
Mr. Laurier, we have a warrant to search your apartm...
哪里跑 Oliver
Don't run, Oliver.
Booth探员认为 你可能有某样
Agent Booth is under the impression that you might have
与他手上的案子相关的证物
something pertinent to a case he's working on.
你们在找青铜星章吗
You're looking for a Bronze Star?
像Cleo戴的那种吗
Like the one Cleo wore?
就是那块 Mr. Laurier
Exactly like that one, Mr. Laurier.
我没有
I don't have it.
有时候跟踪狂会留纪念品
Sometimes stalkers retain keepsakes.
这尼玛都是什么
What the hell are these things, huh?
圣徒生活缩影
Miniature Lives of the Saints.
- 我把它们分...  - 注意头 Bones
- OK. I hand them out... - Heads up, Bones.
我把它们分出去搞慈善
I hand them out for donations.
我不是乞丐 随便拿
I'm not a panhandler. Help yourself.
我没有跟踪过Cleo
I never stalked Cleo.
那为什么她申请了限制令
Then why'd she get a restraining order?
好吧 不是这样的
Ok. Ok. No.
真的搞错了
First of all, no.
她男友Ken Thompson和议员上司
Ken Thompson, her supposed boyfriend, got the restraining order,
申请的限制令
with his boss, the Senator,
Ken只在乎他的工作和热带鱼
but Ken is only concerned with his job and his tropical fish.
他们合谋毁我名誉
They colluded to ruin my reputation
诬陷我是"跟踪狂"  可事实上
with this specious "Stalker" Label, when, in actuality...
我是Cleo的好朋友
...I was Cleo's close friend.
那你为什么看到搜查令要跑
Then why'd you run from the warrant?
三十六计 走为上计
My fight-or-flight response is heavily weighted towards flight.
如果有什么我能帮你们
If there's anything I can do...
抓住杀Cleo的凶手 尽管说
to help you catch Cleo's killer, just tell me.
一整套供词啊  真不错
Oh, a full confession, that would be great.
我爱Cleo
I love Cleo.
我为什么要伤害她
Why would I hurt her?
不介意的话 我留一本小册子
If you don't mind, I'm gonna keep one of these little books.
随意拿吧  Dr. Brennan
Whatever you need... Dr. Brennan.
这是粗略成像 但你肯定明白
This is a rough composite, but you get the idea.
颅骨损伤并不是死因
Skull trauma was not the cause of death.
Cleo先是被刺伤
Cleo was stabbed first.
军用匕首 共5至8刀
She was stabbed five to eight times with a military issue K-Bar knife.
我刚做成了动画
I just completed this rendering.
她手上的自卫伤说明
The defensive wounds to the bones of her hands suggest
在第3或第4次攻击以后
that it wasn't until the third or the fourth penetration...
那刀看起来像是致命的  就那儿
That's likely the fatal stab, right there.
...Cleo才没再反击
...that Cleo stopped fighting back.
我认为 她指骨末梢上
I believe that the distinctive damage
也就是指尖处明显的伤痕
to her distal phalanges -- the tips of her finger bones--
是凶手用刀移开她的指腹造成的
was caused by the murderer using the knife to remove her finger pads.
头骨碎片显示  当时受害人头部
Cranial fragmentation suggests a 20-pound hammer striking four to five times
是处在含硅藻土的水泥地板上
while the victim's head rested on a cement floor
被20磅重的锤子击打4至5次
containing traces of diatomaceous earth.
这个解释和她头骨上的微粒吻合
That's the best explanation for the particulates found in her skull.
这不是一时冲动犯案
This was not a crime of passion.
Cleo并没看见有人要刺她
Cleo never saw the first stab coming.
所以不是争论所致
It didn't arise out of an argument.
为什么要破坏Cleo的脸
Why smash Cleo's face?
为什么要削去指尖
Why whittle away her fingertips,
拿掉她的衣服和首饰
remove her clothing and her jewelry?
还沉尸呢
Sink her body...
比起犯案 凶手倒是花了更多时间
The murderer put more effort into hiding the victim's identity
抹去受害人的身份
than he did into the murder itself.
以免Cleo身份被确认 凶手还伪造证据
In case Cleo was identified, the murderer planted evidence.
Brennan从跟踪狂那里拿的小册子
The little book Brennan got from the stalker
与Cleo手上找到的纤维相符
matches the cellulose found in Cleo's hand.
军人墓地 军刀
Military cemetery, military knife,
都误导性暗示是她父亲所为
implicates her own father, more misdirection.
听起来像个阴险的傻缺议员呢
Sound like any conniving son-of-a-bitch senators you know?
你们指望我 凭这全息图像水晶球
You expect me to declare war on a United States senator
就向一位美国参议员宣战
based on your little holographic crystal ball?
这不是魔法
It's not magic.
这是案件基于证据的逻辑再现
It's a logical recreation of events based on evidence.
这比我的直觉好不到哪去
It's no more valid than my gut.
一个好的假设得经得起测试
A good hypothesis with stands testing.
才是可信的假设
That's what makes it a good hypothesis.
跟假设无关
Not a hypothesis
你们只有一具女尸和一位美国议员
You have a dead girl and a United States senator.
这是为啥眯眯眼只配呆在实验室
This is exactly why squints belong in the lab.
你们根本不明白外面的世界
You guys don't know anything about the real world.
走吧 我们说完了
Come on. We're done here.
好敏感哟
Touchy!
你肯定知道她家的事
You must know about her family.
在她15岁时双亲失踪
Both parents vanish when she's 15.
也能算现实的残酷吧
Probably counts as the real world.
我知道她的事
Yeah, I know the story.
我读过文件
I read the file.
警方没有任何线索
The cops never found out anything.
Brennan觉得
Brennan figures that...
也许有人跟她的遭遇相同
maybe if somebody like her had been there...
作为一个讨厌心理学的人
Well, for somebody who hates psychology,
她懂得不少啊
she sure has a lot of it.
就知道能在这里找到你
Thought I'd find you here.
好枪法和练武术
You know, you being a good shot and doing martial arts,
是你的排解方式
it's all your way of dealing.
谁还能比你更清楚生命的脆弱
I mean, who knows better than you how fragile life can be?
曾经的陆军突击狙击手
Maybe an Army Ranger sniper
现在的FBI凶案调查员呗
who became an FBI homicide investigator.
噢你也查过我呢
Oh, you looked me up, huh?
介意不
Do you mind?
- 随意  - 谢了
- Be my guest.  - Thank you.
你以前也就这水平吗
Were you any good at being a sniper?
狙击手能觉察到杀手的气场什么的
A sniper gets to know a little something about killers.
Bethlehem议员 不是凶手
Senator Bethlehem, he's no killer.
那么Oliver Laurier就是了
Oh, and Oliver Laurier is?
依我看 他就一神经病
Way I read Laurier, he's unhinged.
所以他才危险
That makes him dangerous.
这一定又是你的直觉 是吧
That'd be your "Gut" Telling you that, correct?
谋杀案呢
You know, homicides?
可不是科学家破的
They're not solved by scientists.
是被我这种人解决掉的
They're solved by guys like me
不停地问各种问题
asking a thousand questions a thousand times,
揪出每次说谎的人
catching people telling lies every time.
你的工作你在行 Bones
You're great at what you do, Bones, but...
可你破不了案子
you don't solve murders...
警察能
Cops do.
Cleo Eller遇害的地方
Cleo Eller was killed
是撒有硅藻土的水泥地板上
on a cement floor sprinkled with diatomaceous earth.
血迹还在地板上
Traces of her blood will still be in that cement.
或者咱俩之一错了 或者都错了
One of us is wrong, maybe both of us,
但如果Bethlehem不是议员
but if Bethlehem wasn't a senator,
你可能已经在他家地下室
you'd be right there in his basement
找案发现场
looking for that killing floor.
你害怕他
You're afraid of him.
你的假设是 眯眯眼破不了案而警察能
Your hypothesis is that squints don't solve murders and cops do.
证明给我看啊
Prove it.
做个警察
Be a cop.
Booth
Booth?
他们看起来很高兴 是吧
They look pretty happy, don't they?
否则他们也不会录下来
Otherwise they wouldn't turn on the camera, I guess.
听Zack说你想见我
Zack said you wanted to see me.
谈谈你不想提的事
Something you don't like to talk about :
家庭
families.
Temperance
Temperance...
搭档会分享信息
partners, they share things.
才能建立互信
Builds trust.
我们啥时候成搭档了
Since when are we partners?
我为我的臆断道歉
I apologize for the assumption.
你申请了Bethlehem家的搜查令
You got a warrant to search Bethlehem's place?
你说的对
You were right :
如果Bethlehem不是参议员
If Bethlehem wasn't a senator,
我会在地下室里寻找凶杀现场
I'd be in that basement, looking for that killing floor.
但你错的是
But you're wrong.
我不是怕他
I was never afraid of that guy.
我这么做也不是因为你是天才
And I'm not doing this because you're a genius.
我是为了Cleo
I'm doing this for Cleo.
搜查令上说他们在找血迹
The warrant says they're searching for blood traces,
大铁锤和硅藻土
a sledgehammer and diatomaceous earth.
那些是什么东西
What the hell is that?
你犯了个大错
You're making a big mistake.
我只负责...
I'm only in charge...
你插进来破坏了我的调查
You're coming in and mess up my investigation.
愿意做个声明吗 参议员
Care to make a statement, Senator?
Bethlehem参议员 能回答几个问题吗
Senator Bethlehem, can you just answer a couple questions?
谁批准的搜查令 何时批准的
Who gave you this warrant? When was it delivered?
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
瞧瞧他 除了玩弄政治他一无是处
Look at him. For all his politics, he's got nothing.
他应该像我一样深爱Cleo
He should've loved Cleo properly, like I would've.
能给我签个名不
Will you sign my book?
Oliver 再跟踪我 我就揍你
Stalk me, Oliver, and I will kick your ass.
我不认识这东西
I don't recognize that.
那不是我的东西
That is not mine.
那不是我的
That is not mine!
至少我们有锤子了
At least we got the hammer.
但只有这个
Yeah, but that's all we got.
地下室是水泥地面吧
Cement floor in the basement?
是的 但没有血迹没有硅藻土
Yeah, but no blood, no diatomaceous earth.
Bones 我们得一箭三雕
We needed a trifecta, Bones,
物证 凶器 犯罪现场
physical evidence, murder weapon, crime scene.
警察都不拘捕他吗
They wouldn't even arrest him?
别担心
Don't worry.
如果那是杀Cleo Eller的锤子 他跑不了
If that's the hammer used on Cleo Eller, he'll get arrested.
为能抓住那混蛋干杯
A toast... to getting the murderous bastard.
光有锤子不够
The hammer's not enough.
他会逃过去的
He's going to get away with it.
也许Booth是对的
Maybe Booth is right.
出了实验室我就是废柴
Maybe outside the lab, I'm useless.
圣徒生活缩影会指引我们前进的方向
Let us take guidance from The Lives of the Saints.
Albertus Magnus 科学家的守护神
Albertus Magnus, Patron Saint of Scientists.
Albertus Magnus: 中世纪欧洲哲学家 提倡神学与科学和平并存
我以为Magnus是鱼贩子的守护神
I thought Magnus was the patron saint of fishmongers.
他俩不是一人
Two separate entities.
Albertus Magnus是13世纪的哲学家
Albertus Magnus was a 13th-century philosopher.
鱼贩守护神是
The fishmonger saint was...
鱼
Fish!
你说过硅藻土
You said that diatomaceous earth
可以做过滤剂
could be used as a filtering agent.
对 游泳池和滤水器
Yeah, for swimming pools, water filters...
或者热带鱼
Or tropical fish?
Oliver Laurier说Ken Thompson养鱼
Oliver Laurier said that Ken Thompson kept fish.
你急啥
What's your hurry?
Thompson见过搜查令
Thompson read the warrant!
他知道我们在找硅藻土
He knows we're looking for diatomaceous earth!
打电话给Booth
Get in touch with Booth.
告诉他我要去哪儿
Tell him where I'm going, okay?
她其实没说要去哪儿 是吧
She didn't actually say where she was going, did she?
住手 你不能破坏证据
Stop! You can't destroy evidence.
这可是私宅 你没搜查令吧
This is a private residence. I don't suppose you have a warrant?
我跟FBI合作
I'm working with the FBI.
如果我有理由怀疑你正在犯罪
If I have reasonable suspicion of a crime being committed,
就不需要搜查令
I don't need a warrant.
什么罪行
What crime?
破坏联邦调查案件的相关证据
Destruction of evidence pertinent to a federal investigation.
我只是做清洁
I'm just cleaning up.
你喝酒了吧
Is that alcoholy smell on your breath?
这油毡可是新的
This linoleum looks fairly new.
下面是什么 水泥?
What's underneath? Cement?
你打Cleo的头时 嵌她头骨里的
The same cement that was embedded in Cleo's skull
是一样的水泥吧
when you bashed her head in?
你可以走了
You might wanna get out of here.
我不能让你破坏证据
I can't let you destroy evidence.
你怎么阻止我
How are you going to stop me?
我会阻止你的
I'll stop you.
在我烧毁房子之前不可能了
Not before I burn this place down
连你一起烧了
with you in it.
我不明白
I don't get it.
不是因为嫉妒和愤怒失控
It wasn't jealousy, it wasn't passion.
Cleo不想做掉你老板的孩子
Cleo wouldn't get rid of your boss's baby,
你就把她做掉了
and so you got rid of her.
这是什么心理 你算什么人啊
What kind of psychology is that? What kind of person are you?
Temperance
Temperance...
你还好吧
Are you all right?
Oliver 我知道你来这
Oliver, I understand you're here
是误认为我有危险
out of a misguided concern for my safety,
但显然我看人不怎么准
but I apparently don't read people very well,
而你可能在精神上支持Ken
and you could be in some kind of psychotic collusion with Ken,
所以我要你去那里
so I'm going to ask you to go over there
按住他的伤口
and apply pressure to his wound
直到警察过来 明白吗
until the police get here, you understand?
好 是他杀了Cleo吗
OK. OK. Did he kill Cleo?
对 他杀了Cleo
Yeah. He killed Cleo.
好吧  那么
Okay... then...
我就看着他流血至死呗
I'm down with him bleeding to death.
如果他死了
That guy bleeds to death,
Bones会因蓄意谋杀罪受审
Bones will go on trial for attempted murder.
你不想那样 是吧
You don't want that, now,do you?
我不想
I wouldn't want that.
另外伤口被按压会非常疼
Besides, you know applying pressure that can be very painful.
证据显示是他干的
The evidence said he did it, but...
但我不明白原因
I don't know why.
不  那不重要
No, it doesn't matter.
知道吗 动机并不重要
You know what? Motive does not matter.
他这么做是为了保住工作
He did it to save his job.
工作
His job?
议员被曝丑闻 他就前程无亮了
Yeah, senator in scandal, he'll lose the beltway fast track.
就这么简单
It's that simple, it's...
此地生活残酷嘛
It's a tough town.
对 这里生活是不容易
Yeah, it is a tough town.
以后有机会
Yeah, you know in the future,
开枪的事由我来
maybe I should do the shooting.
为什么 我枪法很好
Why? I'm a good shot.
主啊 使我成为你和平的使者
Lord, make me an instrument of Your peace.
在愤恨之处 让我播种爱
Where there is hatred, let me sow love.
在伤害之处 播种宽恕
Where there is injury, pardon.
FBI会起诉Brennan吗
Is the FBI gonna lay charges against Brennan?
她只朝他的腿 打了一枪
She only shot him in the leg... once.
她没有事先警告
She didn't give him a warning.
直接开枪前还喝过酒
She just shot him, with alcohol on her breath.
这是她第一次射击
It was her first shooting.
初出茅庐你能指望她有多完美
You can't expect her to be perfect right out of the gate.
你狙击别人前都给几次警告
How much warning did you give people before you sniped them?
在怀疑之处 播种信心
Where there's doubt, faith.
在绝望之处 播种希望
Where there's despair, hope.
在幽暗之处 播种光明
Where there's darkness, light.
怎么
What?
我告诉你不是议员
I told you it wasn't the Senator.
可我告诉你谁是凶手了 咱俩扯平
And I told you who it was, so we're even.
只是我们在办同一个案子
Except we work on the same cases,
而纽约时报畅销书单上 你却榜上有名
and you end up on the New York Times bestsellers list.
我还不知道呢
I didn't know that.
第三名 新晋热门
Number three, with a bullet.
很好 对吧
That's good, right?
纽约时报 新晋热门
The New York Times, with a bullet?
你要发了 通知你的会计师
Means you're rich, call your accountant.
我没有会计
I don't have an accountant.
那赶紧找一个
Well, get one.
好吧 要怎么做
Okay. How does that work?
你要走出实验室 懂不
You need to get out of the lab, you know?
看电视 听广播 啥都行
Watch TV, turn on a radio, anything.
拿起电话
Pick up the phone, and...
在悲伤之处 播种欢乐
Where there is sadness, joy.
哦 神圣的主啊
Oh, Divine Master, grant that
愿我能安慰他人 多于被安慰
I may seek not so much to be consoled, as to console...
理解他人 多于被理解
to be understood, as to understand...
爱人 多于被爱
to be loved, as to love.
因为在给予中...
For it is in giving...
如果不是你
You know, if it weren't for you...
他们永远不会知道
those people would never have known
他们的女儿的遭遇
what happened to their daughter.
这比知道真相还糟
That's got to be worse than the truth.
我知道Ellers夫妇对Cleo的感受
I know exactly how the Ellers felt about Cleo.
15岁时 我父母失踪了
My parents disappeared when I was 15,
没人知道他们怎么了
and nobody knows what happened to them.
作为狙击手 我夺走了许多生命
Being a sniper, I... took a lot of lives.
我在有生之年能做的
What I'd like to do before I'm done
就是抓更多的杀人犯
is try and catch at least that many murderers.
拜托 你不觉得这有点像
Please, you don't think there's some kind of...
因果循环
cosmic balance sheet.
我愿意帮你实现你的愿望
I'd like to help you with that.